Address

Phone | Smkayat@berkeley.edu | ₩ill creaate one! | In https://www.linkedin.com/in/kazem-ayat-3b7229161/

Research Interests

I am in love with physics and astrophysics/astronomy. I like to participate in theory or experimental researches. My intresets are but not limited to Astronomy, cosmology, biophysics, nuclear physics, atomic physics, and plasma physics. I love to use physics and find applications in the real world. I love to add something good to this world with my physics:)

Education

University Of California: Berkeley

Berkeley, Ca

Expected Graduation date: By the End of

Fall 2023

In progress bachelor's degree of Physics

- Quantum Mechanics 1 (137A) —4 units
- Math Methods for Physics students (89) —4 units
- Analytical Mechanics (105)—4 units
- · Quantum Mechanics 2 (137B)—4 units
- Instrumentational Laboratory and electronics (111A)—4 units
- Python Decal (Astron 89)—2 units
- Advanced Physics Laboratory (111B)— 3 units in progress
- Statistical Mechanics (112) 4 units in progress

West Valley College San Jose, Ca

Associate degrees in Physics and Mathematics

San Jose, Ca AUG 2018 - April 2021

Research and Work Experience

University of California: Berkeley (Research at Prof. Imke de Pater Group)

Berkeley, Ca

Analyzing the Uranus' Rings

SEP 2021 - Current

- Data Analysis
- Aperture Photometry
- Coding
- Fits File Masking
- Technical Skills: Python with Photutils, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Astroquary, astropy
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

West Valley College — Instructional Lab Technician (Lab tech assistant)

San Jose, Ca

Physical Science Department of the West Valley College

Jan 2019 - August 2021

- Designed and constructed new laboratory apparatus for physics labs and classroom demonstrations
- Created exercises for students based around new laboratory apparatus
- Assisted students with troubleshooting technical problems during physics labs
- Fits File Masking
- Organized and maintained a physics stockroom (with astronomy and geology rooms)
- Setting up the labs for students
- Mini in-lab research

Projects

Python Decal End of Semester Project: Simulating a Foreign Planetary System

UC Berkeley, CA

UC Berkeley

Developing a team-based project to simulate a foreign planetary system containing one star and five planets

• Leading and managing the team (consists of 5 members).

Morse transmitter and receiver

UC Berkeley, CA Nov 2022 - DEC 2022

UC Berkeley

• Created a circuit with many subvi's to transmit morse code using an LED.

FEBRUARY 12, 2023

Skills

Python Programming Well experienced in Python (Pandas, NumPy, matplotlib, scipy, astropy, etc

LabView Programming Well experienced in LabView programming.

Latex LaTeX proficiency

C Programming Experienced in C programming.

Linux, Kali Linux Experienced in Linux and Kali Linux

Java Programming Well experienced in Java programming

CSS/HTML/JavaScript Some Experiences in CSS/HTML/JavaScript.

SAOImage DS9 Image Processing and data visualization application

PCB Design PCB design, and Kicad software skills

Soft Skill Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

Complete Later_____

Languages _____

English Fluent **Persian** Fluent